Guide to the Olga Rudge Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- General Correspondence, 1904-89; Series II; 29.5; (60 boxes)
  - Lavocat, Moussia, 1951-60 (Box 53, Folder 1443)
  - Lawton, Ralph, 1935-62, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1444-46)
  - Lees, David, 1957-82, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1447)
  - Lenzoni de Ojeda, Fabiola, 1949-64, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1448)
  - Levi, Giorgio, 1938, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 1449)
  - Levi, Rafaello, 1947-57 (Box 53, Folder 1450)
  - Levy, Alan, 1970-85, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1451)
  - Lewcowicz, Henri, 1952-54 (Box 53, Folder 1452)
  - Liani, Davide, 1985-86, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1453)
  - Library of Congress, 1939-75 (Box 53, Folder 1454)
  - Lippi, Simonetta, 1954-67 (Box 53, Folder 1455-64)
  - Lippi, Simonetta, 1968-72, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1465-71)
  - Little Orchestra Society, Ltd., 1952, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 1472)
  - Littlefield, Lester, 1960-73, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1473-90)
  - Littlefield, Lester, 1970-73, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1490-1500)
  - Livi, Grazia, 1962-72, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1501)
  - Longo, Giorgio, 1972 Nov 2
  - Longworth, Alice Roosevelt, 1973 Jan 15
  - Lorenzatos, Zissimos, 1966-76 (Box 55, Folder 1502)
  - Lovatelli, Filippo, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 1503)
  - Lowell, Robert, 1966 May 6
  - Luciani, Sebastiano Arturo, 1939-50, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1504-12)
  - "M" general, 1920-88, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1513-25)
    Includes: Gerald Malanga, T. S. Matthews, Anna Motto, John Warner Moore, Jan Morris
  - Maazel, Lorin, 1955, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1526)
  - MacGregor, Robert (New Directions), 1952-72 (Box 56, Folder 1527-29)
  - MacKenzie, Faith Compton, [1958] (Box 56, Folder 1530)
  - McKeown, Thomas, 1975, n.d.
  - McKibbin, David, 1947
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1975, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1531)
    See also: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3701
  - McMillar, Pam, 1983, n.d.
  - McNab, Constance, 1968-88, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1532)
  - MacNaughton, William, 1968-83 (Box 56, Folder 1533)
  - MacShane, Frank, 1968-77 (Box 56, Folder 1534)
  - Maglini, Ruggero, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 1535)
  - Maitland, Robert
  - Majno, Luigi, 1971-75 (Box 56, Folder 1536-39)
  - Majno, Luigi, 1976-86, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1540-41)
  - Malherbe, Dom de, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 1542)
  - Maline, Julian, 1930-63, m.d. (Box 57, Folder 1543)
  - Mandiargues, Bona de, 1970-72 (Box 57, Folder 1544)
  - Manera, Giorgio, 1972-83, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1545-46)
  - Mangione, Laura, 1969-73 (Box 57, Folder 1547-49)
  - Marcher, Johanna, 1925-51, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1550-55)
  - M'Arte Edizioni
    See: Luigi Majno, Box 56, folder 1536
  - Martinelli, Sheri, 1984 Apr 23 (Box 57, Folder 1556)
  - Martz, Louis, 1973 Jul 4 (Box 57, Folder 1557)
  - Mathes, James, 1980-88, n.d.
  - Matz, Charles, 1964-75 (Box 57, Folder 1558-59)
  - Matz, Mary Jane, 1965-83, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1560-63)
  - Matz family, 1964-87, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1564)
  - Mazzini, Francesca, 1961-81, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1565)
  - Melton, Lindy, 1934-74, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1566-68)
  - Menotti, Gian Carlo, 1964-73, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1569)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1952-53 (Box 58, Folder 1570)
  - Meylan, Raymond, 1949 Nov 25 (Box 58, Folder 1571)
  - Milré, Jennifer Milré, Yvon, 1973-85, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1572-74)
  - Mistral, Gabriela, 1951-54 (Box 58, Folder 1575)
  - Monotti, Francesco, 1933-61, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1576)
  - Montanari, Franco, 1967-72 (Box 58, Folder 1577)
  - Monti, Rolando, 1976-85, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1578)
  - Moore, Frank L., 1948, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1579)
  - Morgan, Priscilla, 1970, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 1580)
  - Mori, Giuseppe, 1941 Dec 7
  - Mortimer, Raymond, 1979 Nov 2
  - Münch, Gerhart, 1934-57 (Box 58, Folder 1581)
  - "N" general, 1940-87, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1582-83)
    Includes Charles Norman
  - Naldi, Norah, 1941-63, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1584-87)
  - Nardi, Piero, 1964-67, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1588)
  - Neame, Alan, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 1589)
  - Nebolsine, Arcadii, 1971-81, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1590)
  - New Directions, 1948-82 (Box 58, Folder 1591-92)
    See also: James Laughlin, Box 53, folder 1434
    See also: Robert MacGregor, Box 56, folder 1527
  - New York Center for Visual History, 1981-84 (Box 58, Folder 1593)
  - New York Public Library, 1981 Dec (Box 58, Folder 1594)
  - New Yorker, 1960-72, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1595)
  - Niccoli, Raffaello, 1959-72 (Box 58, Folder 1596)
  - Nocher, Graziella, 1958-85, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1597-1604)
  - Noguchi, Isamu, 1970-75, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1605)
  - "O" general, 1955-87, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1606-07)
  - Obermer, Dr., 1929 (Box 59, Folder 1608)
  - O'Grady, Desmond, 1961-89, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1609-16)
  - Overholser, Winifred
    See: Saint Elizabeth's Hospital, Box 72, folder 1972
  - Ozturk, Tony, 1980-83, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1617)
  - "P" general, 1924-88, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1618-21)
  - Paczosa, Evelyn, 1938-81, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1622)
  - Padero, G., 1933 (Box 60, Folder 1623)
  - Page, Chester, 1988 Jul 3 (Box 60, Folder 1624)
  - Paideuma, 1973-85 (Box 60, Folder 1625)
    See also: Terrell, Carroll F., Box 80, folder 2158
  - Paige, Douglas D., 1947-72, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1626-29)
  - Palandri, Angela, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 1630)
  - Palmer, Martin, 1953-72, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1631)
  - Pantano, Antonio, 1983-88, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1632)
  - Paquette, Donald J., 1950 (Box 60, Folder 1633)
  - Pardo de Santayana, Jesús, 1974 Oct 5 (Box 60, Folder 1634)
  - Paterson, Katherine, 1972, n.d.
  - Paterson, Mary, 1983-88 (Box 60, Folder 1635)
  - Patmore, Brigit, 1930 Oct 30
  - Pea, Enrico, 1947-52, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1636-38)
  - Pearlman, Daniel, 1968-72, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1639)
  - Pearn, Pollinger & Higham, Ltd., 1951, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 1640)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1953-75 (Box 60, Folder 1641)
  - Pellegrini family, 1956-78, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1642-43)
  - Pelizzi, Camilio, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 1644)
  - Pensione Seguso, 1957, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1645)
  - Periccioli, Ugo, 1956-58 (Box 60, Folder 1646-47)
  - Perry, Julia, 1956-72, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1648-49)
  - Pescetto, Alberto, 1951-61 (Box 60, Folder 1650-53)
  - Pescetto, Alberto, 1962-80, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1654-62)
  - Peterich, Berthe, 1959-72, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1663-64)
  - Peterkiewicz, Jerzy, 1982-85, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1665)
  - Pettinelli, Lina, 1952-69 (Box 61, Folder 1666-67)
  - Picabia, Gabrielle, 1954-55 (Box 61, Folder 1668)
  - Picardi, Rudolph, 1953-59 (Box 61, Folder 1669)
  - Piller, Boaz, 1957-61, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1670)
  - Pincherle, Marc, 1948-64, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1671)
  - Pitkethly, Lawrence
    See: New York Center for Visual History, Box 58, folder 1593
  - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1920-60 (Box 61, Folder 1672-73)
  - Pizzorno, Vittorina
    See: Vittorina De Barbieri Pizzorno, Box 61, folder 1672
  - Pöldinger, Walter, Dr., 1966-68 (Box 61, Folder 1674)
  - Polignac, Winaretta de, 1930-39, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1675-77)
  - Por, Odon, 1957 Nov 27 (Box 61, Folder 1678)
  - Potier, Adrian de, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1679)
  - Poujol, Marc, 1960, 1962
  - Pound, Dorothy, 1943-64 (Box 61, Folder 1680-85)
  - Pound, Dorothy, 1965-72, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1686-1700)
  - Pound, Elizabeth, 1975, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1701)
  - Pound, Ezra
    See: Series I, Boxes 1-32 and Box 83, folder 2238
  - Pound, Homer, 1933-38 (Box 62, Folder 1702)
  - Pound, Isobel, [1938], 1946 (Box 62, Folder 1703)
  - Pound, Omar, 1970-83 (Box 62, Folder 1704-06)
  - Pound, Oriana, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 1707)
  - Puccetti, Gabriella
    See: Gabriella Bairo Puccetti, Box 62, folder 1707
  - Pujol, E., 1953-62 (Box 62, Folder 1708)
  - Purves, Drika, 1984-85 (Box 62, Folder 1709)
  - "Q" general, 1972-84 (Box 62, Folder 1710)
  - Quill, Sarah, 1982-84 (Box 62, Folder 1711)
  - Quinn, Bernetta, Sister, 1967-87, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1712-15)
  - "R" general, 1948-84, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1716-18)
  - Rachewiltz, Boris de, 1951-84, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1719-23)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1930-37 (Box 63, Folder 1724-35)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1938-40 (Box 64, Folder 1736-58)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1941-44 (Box 65, Folder 1759-81)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1945-55 (Box 66, Folder 1782-1810)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1956-61 (Box 67, Folder 1811-40)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1962-89, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1841-68)
  - Rachewiltz, Patrizia de
    See: Patrizia de Rachewiltz de Vroom, Box 81, folder 2185
  - Rachewiltz, Walter de, 1955-89, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1869-79)
  - Rainer, Dachine, 1973-89, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1880-83)
  - Ramsey, Gloria, 1951-83, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1884-89)
  - Rawlings, John, 1974-79, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1890)
  - Read, Forrest, 1962-78, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1891-92)
  - Reck, Michael, 1967-72, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1893-94)
  - Reid, Albert Reid, Ethel, 1964-87, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1895-1903)
  - Reid, Olga, 1969-84, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1904-08)
  - Reyes, Emma
    See: Emma Ivancich Reyes, Box 70, folder 1371
  - Reyes, Lilia Teresita, 1960-62 (Box 70, Folder 1909)
  - Richards, Cicely, 1962, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1910)
  - Richards, Grace, 1933-40, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1911)
  - Rinaldi, Mario, 1942-57 (Box 70, Folder 1912)
  - Ringer, Gordon, 1950 Apr 11 (Box 70, Folder 1913)
  - Ritt, Ernst, 1987-88 (Box 70, Folder 1914)
  - Robinson, Nicholas, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 1915)
  - Rodes, J. M., 1942 Jun 13
  - Romero, Philip, 1986, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1916)
  - Roncaglia, Gino, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 1917)
  - Ronsisvalle, Vanni, 1966-72 (Box 70, Folder 1918)
  - Root, Waverly Lewis, 1932 Feb 13 (Box 70, Folder 1919)
  - Roux, Dominique de, 1963-72, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1920-27)
  - Roux, J[acqueline?], 1961-63, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1928)
  - Rudge, Arthur, 1918 (Box 70, Folder 1929)
  - Rudge, J. Edgar, 1928-31 (Box 70, Folder 1930)
  - Rudge, Jane, 1937 (Box 70, Folder 1931)
  - Rudge, Julia O'Connell, 1904-07, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1932)
  - Rudge, Katherine, 1935-52, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1933)
  - Rudge, Peter, 1948-85, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1934-36)
  - Rudge, Teddy, 1918-79, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1937-52)
  - Rupnik, Emerico, 1952-54 (Box 71, Folder 1953)
  - Russell, Peter, 1948-63 (Box 71, Folder 1954-56)
  - Russell, Peter, 1964-79, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1957-61)
  - Rylands, Jane Turner, 1981-88, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1962)
  - "S" general, 1927-88, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1963-70)
  - Sabatini, Renzo, 1953, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 1971)
  - Saint Elizabeths Hospital, 1948-52 (Box 72, Folder 1972)
  - Sakharoff, Clotilde, 1954-63 (Box 72, Folder 1973)
  - Sale, Annamaria, 1969
  - Santomaso, Giuseppe, 1970, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 1974)
  - Santo Stefano, Giovanna, 1951-65 (Box 72, Folder 1975)
  - Scarpellini, Fernando, 1949-54 (Box 72, Folder 1976)
  - Scheiwiller, Giovanni (Vanni), 1956-58 (Box 72, Folder 1977-81)
  - Scheiwiller, Giovanni (Vanni), 1959-88, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1982-93)
  - Schellhous, Edward, 1962, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1994)
  - Schneider, Edouard, 1927-58 (Box 73, Folder 1995-97)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, 1961 May 22 (Box 73, Folder 1998)
  - Seelye, Catherine, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 1999)
  - Segovia, Andrès, 1956, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2000)
  - Selden-Goth, Gisella, 1951-62, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2001)
  - Sell, Henry, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 2002)
  - Sella, Marta, 1955-74, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2003-09)
  - Sergeant, Winthrop
    See: New Yorker, Box 58, folder 1595
  - Serly, Tibor, 1936-72, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2010)
  - Serrano, Miguel, 1972-83 (Box 73, Folder 2011)
  - Severs, Jin, 1953-55, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2012)
  - Shewring. Walter, 1949-74, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2013)
  - Sian, Goh Peck, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2014)
  - Sides, Patricia, 1967-72, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 2015)
  - Sieveking, M., n.d.
  - Sigma-Tau, 1963, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 2016-17)
  - Silk, Samuel
    See: Saint Elizabeths Hospital, Box 72, folder 1972
  - Simpson, Dallam, 1947-51 (Box 74, Folder 2018)
  - Singh, G., 1967-88, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 2019-25)
  - Slavin, George, 1965-69 (Box 75, Folder 2026-44)
  - Slavin, George, 1970-72 (Box 76, Folder 2045-64)
  - Slavin, George, 1973, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 2066-72)
  - Slocovich, Ettore, 1954-59, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2073)
  - Smith, Dryden Gilling, 1951
  - Snyder, Robert, 1960-71 (Box 78, Folder 2074-78)
  - Solane, Janine, 1954-89, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2079-99)
  - Somers-Cocks, Blanche, 1945-57, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2100-09)
  - Somers-Cocks, John, 1948 Sep 18 (Box 79, Folder 2110)
  - Sominelli, Rita, 1957-69 (Box 79, Folder 2111)
  - Spencer, Delta, 1954-68, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2112)
  - Spina, Ribelle, 1954-60 (Box 79, Folder 2113)
  - Spoken Arts, Inc., 1965-66 (Box 79, Folder 2114)
  - Stambler, Bernard, 1952 Aug 17 (Box 79, Folder 2115)
  - Stern, Richard, 1962-82 (Box 79, Folder 2116-17)
  - Stocchi, Gabriele Stocchi, Luisa, 1955-86, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2118-23)
  - Stock, Marjorie, 1967, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 2124)
  - Stock, Noel, 1966-68
  - Stokes, Adrian, 1927-49, n.d (Box 79, Folder 2125-28)
  - Storch, Laila, 1950-79, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2129-30)
  - Strale, Marguerite, 1952-73, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2131-34)
  - Stricchi, Marilu, 1949-60, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2135)
  - Stroumillo, Olga de (Nelly), 1945-88, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2136-42)
  - Studer, Clara, 1946 (Box 80, Folder 2143)
  - Sugar, Lolette de, 1962-71, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2144-45)
  - Sullivan, Janet, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 2146)
  - Swabey, Henry, 1945-72, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2147-48)
  - Szasz, Thomas S., 1973-83 (Box 80, Folder 2149)
  - "T" general, 1934-87, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2150-53)
  - Takahashi, Isao, 1961-62 (Box 80, Folder 2154)
  - Tappe, Horst, 1963-79, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2155-56)
  - Tate Gallery, 1980-88 (Box 80, Folder 2157)
  - Tellini, Inés Alfani
    See: Inés Alfani Tellini, Box 80, folder 2157
  - Terrell, Carroll F., 1973-85 (Box 80, Folder 2158)
  - Terribili, Anita, 1951-63
  - Thiele-Dorfman, Klaus, 1984-87 (Box 80, Folder 2159)
  - Thoresby, Christina, 1972-85, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2160)
  - Tissot, Lin, 1956, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2161)
  - Torre, Bona, 1970-84, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2162)
  - Tortora, Vincent, 1966-73 (Box 80, Folder 2163)
  - Tosi, Sandra, 1956-58, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2164)
  - Tytell, John, 1985-86, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2165)
  - United States Army, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 2166)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1962 Feb 26 (Box 80, Folder 2167)
  - United States Foreign Service, 1945-69 (Box 80, Folder 2168)
  - United States Supreme Court, 1940 May 31 (Box 80, Folder 2169)
  - "V" general, 1939-87, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 2170-71)
  - Valeri, Diego, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 2172)
  - Vallerino, Elisa, 1952-62, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 2173-75)
  - Vannini, Armando, 1935-62, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 2176-82)
  - Vicari, Giambattista, 1957-72 (Box 81, Folder 2183)
  - Volpe, Rino, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 2184)
  - Vroom, Patrizia de Rachewiltz de, 1955-88, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 2185-2201)
  - "W" general, 1941-86, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2202-04)
  - Wagons-Lits/Cook, 1938, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 2205)
  - Wahrent, Bettina, 1953-69, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2206-08)
  - Wallace, Emily, 1973, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 2209)
  - Wallace, William, 1907
  - Walsh, Ernest, 1922-24, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2210)
  - Wang, Lucien, Mrs., 1959-72 (Box 82, Folder 2211-12)
  - Whigham, Peter, 1964 Jul 1 (Box 82, Folder 2213)
  - Whittaker, W. Gillies, 1936
  - Wickes, George, 1972-73 (Box 82, Folder 2214)
  - Widershien, Mark, 1975-83 (Box 82, Folder 2215)
  - Wilhelm, James J., 1982-88, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2216)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1977-84 (Box 82, Folder 2217)
  - Winner, Christopher, 1978-79, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2218)
  - Wolfe, Judith, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 2219)
  - Wood, Michael
    See: Foyer, Box 47, folder 1277
  - Woodson, Anne, 1983, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2220)
  - Wrage, Klaus, 1959-66 (Box 82, Folder 2221)
  - Wright, William, 1964-66 (Box 82, Folder 2222)
  - Wykes-Joyce, Max, 1949-83, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2223)
  - "Y" general, 1956, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2224)
  - Yagi, Mariyo, 1972-78, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2225)
  - Yale University Library, 1962-88 (Box 82, Folder 2226)
    See also: Donald Gallup, Box 48, folder 1297
  - "Z" general, 1954-80, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2227)
  - Zacconi, Norina, 1985, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 2228)
  - Zaniboni, Elena, 1962-66, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2229-30)
  - Zeffirelli, Franco, 1950-51, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2231)
  - Zennaro, Elena, 1968-82, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2232-36)
  - Zinnes, Harriet, 1969-79, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2237)
  - Letterbook of Olga Rudge, 1945-46 (Box 83, Folder 2238)
  - First name only A-Z, 1928-86, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 2239-44)
  - Unidentified, 1950-88, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 2245-52)
  - Unidentified, 1950-88, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 2253-59)
  - Empty envelopes, 1918-ca. 1960 (Box 85, Folder 2260-70)
  - Empty envelopes, 1960-69 (Box 86, Folder 2271-81)
  - Empty envelopes, 1970-ca. 1980 (Box 87, Folder 2282-91)
  - Empty envelopes, 1980-89 (Box 88, Folder 2292-2301)
  - Empty envelopes, 1980-89, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 2302-11)
  - Empty envelopes, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2312-17)
  - THIRD PARTY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Allen, Robert to Frumi, Maria, 1973 Oct 1 (Box 91, Folder 2318)
    - Angeli, Helen to Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1963 Jun 22 (Box 91, Folder 2319)
    - Arnold, Kenneth to Laughlin, James, 1977 Sep-Nov (Box 91, Folder 2320)
    - Associazione Italo-Francese di Cultura to Vroom, Patrizia de, 1980 Oct-Nov (Box 91, Folder 2321)
    - Baccardi, Piero to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1939 Oct 25 (Box 91, Folder 2322)
    - Bacigalupo Natali, Frieda to Rachewiltz, Mary de, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2323)
    - Barbetti, Olinto to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1954 Nov 9 (Box 91, Folder 2324)
    - Beikircher, Maria to [Rachewiltz, Mary de], n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2325)
    - Bennett, Mrs. Frank H. to Rachewiltz, Mary and Boris de, 1965 Jun 7 (Box 91, Folder 2326)
    - Bernard, Robert to the Sociéte Internationale des Amis de la Musique Française, 1952 Feb 2 (Box 91, Folder 2327)
    - Berri, Pietro to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1955 Sep 2 (Box 91, Folder 2328)
    - Bird, William to Pound, Dorothy, 1948 Jun 9 (Box 91, Folder 2329)
    - Blazek, Doris to Covington & Burling, 1975-81 (Box 91, Folder 2330)
    - Bohn, Willard to Pound, Dorothy, 1971 Nov 14 (Box 91, Folder 2331)
    - Bregandi, Christophe to Pescetto, Alberto (Box 91, Folder 2332)
    - Bridson, Geoffrey to Pound, Dorothy, 1962 Jun 13 (Box 91, Folder 2333)
    - Bryer, Jackson to Pound, Dorothy, 1966 Jan 30 (Box 91, Folder 2334)
    - Carte Secrete to Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1967 Feb 15 (Box 91, Folder 2335)
    - Cerruti, John M. to Pound, Dorothy, 1963 Apr 15 (Box 91, Folder 2336)
    - Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte to Petit, M. Lyon, 1955 Jul 28 (Box 91, Folder 2337)
    - Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte to Rospigliosi, Clemente, Principe, 1957 Jun 10 (Box 91, Folder 2338)
    - Chiovenda-Petrucci, Annetta to Rachewiltz, Mary de (Box 91, Folder 2339)
    - Christopeit, Walter and Sühnel, Rudolf to Pound, Dorothy, 1962 Jul 15 (Box 91, Folder 2340)
    - Clemens, Cyril to Pound, Dorothy, 1960-67 (Box 91, Folder 2341)
    - Conrad, Andree to Laughlin, James, 1967 Jan 8 (Box 91, Folder 2342)
    - Contino, Vittorugo to Ivancich, Gianfranco, 1974 Mar 16 (Box 91, Folder 2343)
    - Cookson, William to Pound, Dorothy, 1965 Mar 13 (Box 91, Folder 2344)
    - Dadone, Ugo to Vannini, Armando, 1961 May 24 (Box 91, Folder 2345)
    - Davenport, Guy to Pound, Dorothy, !964 Nov 1
    - de Glen, Louis to Glover, Etta, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2346)
    - del Duca, Msr. & Mme. to de Roux, [Comte & Comtesse], [1967 Jun 1] (Box 91, Folder 2347)
    - Doob, Leonard W. to Blazek, Doris, 1975 Jan 22 (Box 91, Folder 2348)
    - Dowlin, John William to Pound, Dorothy, 1962 oct 3 (Box 91, Folder 2349)
    - Drage, M. I. to Pound, Dorothy, 1964 Sep 4 (Box 91, Folder 2350)
    - Driver, Clive E. to Littlefield, Lester, 1972 Oct 19 (Box 91, Folder 2351)
    - Drummond, John to Eliot, T. S., 1953 Sep 10 (Box 91, Folder 2352)
    - Drummond, John to Moore, A. V., 1950 Nov 29 (Box 91, Folder 2353)
    - du Sautoy, Peter to Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1976 May 28 (Box 91, Folder 2354)
    - Duval, Kulgin to Pound, Dorothy, 1967 Feb 27 (Box 91, Folder 2355)
    - Ede, Jim to Philip and Jane Rylands, 1986 Jan (Box 91, Folder 2356)
    - Edwards, John to Heacock, Miss, 1958 Apr 29
    - Etlin, Henri to Burnaym, Edouard, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2357)
    - Fani, Michel to Pound, Dorothy, 1970 Nov 30 (Box 91, Folder 2358)
    - Finthswaite, F. M., Mrs. to Laughlin, James, 1970 Apr 20 (Box 91, Folder 2359)
    - Fondazione Giorgio Cini to Fitzgerald, Joan, 1972 May 8 (Box 91, Folder 2360)
    - Foster, Jean Robert to Pound, Dorothy, 1962 Oct 11 (Box 91, Folder 2361)
    - Francetti, Luigino to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1938 Feb 1 (Box 91, Folder 2362)
    - Friedmann, Louis to Pescetto, Alberto, 1958 Dec 22 (Box 91, Folder 2363)
    - Frogatt, Peter to Singh, G., 1979 Feb 5 (Box 91, Folder 2364)
    - Frumi, Lotte to Rudge, Teddy, 1977 Sep 9 (Box 91, Folder 2365)
    - Gay, Harriet & Larry to Library of Congress, 1983 Apr 8 (Box 91, Folder 2366)
    - Giorgi, Umberto to Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1970 Mar 12 (Box 91, Folder 2367)
    - [Giovannini], Giovanni to Pound, Dorothy, 1962 Oct 21 (Box 91, Folder 2368)
    - Gleason, Herbert P. to Ecklund, John, 1966 Apr 25 (Box 91, Folder 2369)
    - Gleason, Herbert P. to Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1964 Oct 21 (Box 91, Folder 2370)
    - Hamblin, Dodie to Dowd, Jack, 1970 Jul 25 (Box 91, Folder 2371)
    - Hammond, R.M. to Rachewiltz, Walter de, 1966 Apr 8 (Box 91, Folder 2372)
    - Hardman, Joseph M. to von Breidenback, Stueckleberg, 1960 Jun 2 (Box 91, Folder 2373)
    - Harewood, ? to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1950 May 16 (Box 91, Folder 2374)
    - Hawley, W.M. to Pound, Dorothy, 1947 Dec 22 (Box 91, Folder 2375)
    - Hickey, Bernard and Singh, G. to Il Gazzetino de Venezia, 1978 Sep 18 (Box 91, Folder 2376)
    - Hicks, George R. to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1950 Aug 14 (Box 91, Folder 2377)
    - Holden, Barbara B. to Heacock, Esther, 1959 Feb 18 (Box 91, Folder 2378)
    - Horton, David to Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1989 Jul 5 (Box 91, Folder 2379)
    - Hughes, Robert to Cerutti, Sylvio, 1983 Jun 24 (Box 91, Folder 2380)
    - Hynan, Paddy to Matz, Mary Jane, 1970 Jan 24 (Box 91, Folder 2381)
    - Jacomuzzi, Angelo to Singh, G., 1980 Apr 2 (Box 91, Folder 2382)
    - Jerdein, Charles to Unidentified, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2383)
    - Johns Hopkins Press to Rachewiltz, Mary de, [1968 Nov 7] (Box 91, Folder 2384)
    - Kenyon, Harold M. to Laughlin, James, 1947 Jan 11 (Box 91, Folder 2385)
    - Kleeman, Jürg to Bernheimer, Ilse, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2386)
    - Kuntz, Emeric to Guggenheim, Peggy, 1977 Nov 2 (Box 91, Folder 2387)
    - Laughlin, James to Arnold, Kenneth, 1977 Oct 10 (Box 91, Folder 2388)
    - Laughlin, James to Pound, Dorothy, 1945 Nov 4 (Box 91, Folder 2389)
    - Laughlin, James to Tortora, Vincent, 1970 Jun 15 (Box 91, Folder 2390)
    - Lee, Richard to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1947 Feb 21 (Box 91, Folder 2391)
    - Littlefield, Lester to de Rachewiltz, Mary, 1963-72 (Box 91, Folder 2392)
    - Macleod, Joseph Gordon to de Rachewiltz, Mary, 1965 May 30 (Box 92, Folder 2393)
    - Majno, Luigi to Ezra Pound Conference, 1977 Aug 11 (Box 92, Folder 2394)
    - Manera, Giorgio to Yale University, 1975 Apr 19 (Box 92, Folder 2395)
    - Micossi, Maria to Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1960 Oct 4 (Box 92, Folder 2396)
    - Montanari, Filippo to Pound, Dorothy, [1961 Mar 30] (Box 92, Folder 2397)
    - Montgomery, Stuart to Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1968 Dec 15 (Box 92, Folder 2398)
    - Moore, A.V. to Duncan, Ethel, 1954 Dec 14 (Box 92, Folder 2399)
    - Moore, A.V. to Pound, Dorothy, 1964 Jun 24 (Box 92, Folder 2400)
    - Moore, Marianne to Laughlin, James, 1969 Jun 21 (Box 92, Folder 2401)